Al-Shimaa Yehya



Solution Architect





Shimaayahya51@gmail.com 📞 01094640176 🝳 Kafr el-Sheikh 🌐







https://gh2587.github.io/Al-Shimaa-Yehya/

ABOUT ME

Strong believer in the ability of architecture and research combined with design thinking

I started my educational journey in 2017 at the Modern Academy of Engineering and Technology and ended in 2022 with a very good grade. I earned a lot of courses in design

SKILLS

- Good English communication skill in both written English and presentation skills.
- strong experience in Max
- Proven strong experience in CAD, Revit, Max, PowerPoint, and Word programs

3D Max 80% Revit 70% autocad 80% MS Office

EDUCATION

(2017-2022)

MODERN UNIVERSITY

bachelor's degree in architectural engineering

Grade: Very Good

EXPERIENCES

(2018-2019)

SAMA COMPANY

Intern

- Ability to effectively learn and acquire new knowledge and skills. Ability to share knowledge and work in a strong teamoriented environment.
- Develop creative solutions to construction, architectural, or engineering problems

(2021-2022)

ALMUTAHADUH COMPANY

Intern Solution Architect

- Hands-on experience with Revit.
- Assist in Designing, analyzing, and altering plans, prototypes, or structures.
- Identifying and solving problems in building plans, prototypes, and structures.
- Ensuring building systems are functional, reliable, and safe.

